Guide to the Othniel Charles Marsh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General correspondence, 1814-1903; Series I
  - Spalding, William D., 1867; cuid1315 (Box 30, Folder 1294)
  - Spencer, Herbert (1820-1903), 1879-1893; cuid1316 (Box 30, Folder 1295)
  - Sperry, F.L., 1886; cuid1317 (Box 30, Folder 1296)
  - Sperry, L.W., 1890; cuid1318 (Box 30, Folder 1297)
  - Sperry, Lewis (1848-?), 1892; cuid1319 (Box 30, Folder 1297A)
  - Springer, William McKendree (1836-1903), 1886; cuid1320 (Box 30, Folder 1298)
  - Stack, Rohert H., 1874; cuid1321 (Box 30, Folder 1299)
  - Stager, Anson, 1873-1874; cuid1322 (Box 30, Folder 1300)
  - Stanford, Amasa Leland (1824-1893), 1884-1886; cuid1323 (Box 30, Folder 1301)
  - Stanley, Arthur Penrvhn (1851-1881), 1879; cuid1324 (Box 30, Folder 1302)
  - Stanton, Thaddeus H. (?-1900), 1874-1876; cuid1325 (Box 30, Folder 1303)
  - Stanton, Timothy William (1860 - ?), 1894; cuid1326 (Box 30, Folder 1304)
  - Stanton, George D., 1876; cuid1327 (Box 31, Folder 1305)
  - Stayned, Arthur, 1889; cuid1328 (Box 31, Folder 1306)
  - Stearns, Joseph B., 1884; cuid1329 (Box 31, Folder 1307)
  - Stearns, Robert Edwards Carter (1827-1909), 1879; cuid1330 (Box 31, Folder 1308)
  - Stejneger, Leonhard Hess (1851-1943), 1885; cuid1331 (Box 31, Folder 1309)
  - Sternberg, Charles H. (1850-1943), 1884 March - June; cuid1332 (Box 31, Folder 1310)
  - Sternberg, Charles H. (1850-1943), 1884 July; cuid1333 (Box 31, Folder 1311)
  - Sternberg, Charles H. (1850-1943), 1884 August - October; cuid1334 (Box 31, Folder 1312)
  - Sternberg, Charles H. (1850-1943), 1884 November - 1887 December; cuid1335 (Box 31, Folder 1313)
  - Stevens, B.F., 1865-1895; cuid1336 (Box 31, Folder 1314)
  - Stevens, James, 1885; cuid1337 (Box 31, Folder 1314A)
  - Stevens, Richard F., 1868; cuid1338 (Box 31, Folder 1315)
  - Stevens, Walter Le Cone (1847- ?), 1872; cuid1339 (Box 31, Folder 1316)
  - Stevens Brothers, 1864-1865; cuid1340 (Box 31, Folder 1317)
  - Stevenson, James (1840-1888), 1870-1886; cuid1341 (Box 31, Folder 1318)
  - Stevenson, John James (1841-1924), 1878-1889; cuid1342 (Box 31, Folder 1319)
  - Stewart, Alexander Turney (1803-1876), 1868; cuid1343 (Box 31, Folder 1320)
  - Stewart, William Morris (1827-1909), 1892; cuid1344 (Box 31, Folder 1321)
  - Stiles, Charles Wardell (1867-1941), 1893; cuid1345 (Box 31, Folder 1322)
  - Stilwell, L.W., 1889-1890 July; cuid1346 (Box 31, Folder 1323)
  - Stilwell, L.W., 1890 September - 1891; cuid1347 (Box 31, Folder 1324)
  - Stilwell, L.W., 1892; cuid1348 (Box 31, Folder 1325)
  - Stilwell, L.W., 1893-1897; cuid1349 (Box 31, Folder 1326)
  - Stilwell, L.W., 1898-1899; cuid1350 (Box 31, Folder 1327)
  - Stimpson, H.H., 1884-1885; cuid1351 (Box 31, Folder 1328)
  - Stimpson, William (1832-1872), 1867; cuid1352 (Box 31, Folder 1329)
  - Stirling, E.C., 1897; cuid1353 (Box 31, Folder 1330)
  - Stoddard, P.F., 1899; cuid1354 (Box 31, Folder 1331)
  - Stokes, George Gabriel (1819-1903), 1884; cuid1355 (Box 31, Folder 1332)
  - Stoughton, T.M., 1866-1867; cuid1356 (Box 31, Folder 1333)
  - Stoughton, T.M., 1868-1874; cuid1357 (Box 31, Folder 1334)
  - Stoughton, T.M., 1875-1879; cuid1358 (Box 31, Folder 1335)
  - Stoughton, T.M., 1884-1890; cuid1359 (Box 31, Folder 1336)
  - Stoughton, T.M., 1891-1898; cuid1360 (Box 31, Folder 1337)
  - Stover, F.H., 1890; cuid1361 (Box 31, Folder 1338)
  - Stowe, Lewis B., 1869; cuid1362 (Box 31, Folder 1339)
  - Stratton, E.L., 1870; cuid1363 (Box 31, Folder 1340)
  - Strong, S.S., 1868-1870; cuid1364 (Box 32, Folder 1341)
  - Strong, S.S., 1871; cuid1365 (Box 32, Folder 1342)
  - Strong, S.S., 1872-1873; cuid1366 (Box 32, Folder 1343)
  - Strong, S.S., 1874-1876; cuid1367 (Box 32, Folder 1344)
  - Strong, S.S., 1877-1879; cuid1368 (Box 32, Folder 1345)
  - Strong, S.S., 1880-1882; cuid1369 (Box 32, Folder 1346)
  - Struthers, John (1823-1899), 1885; cuid1370 (Box 32, Folder 1347)
  - Struve, C., 1892; cuid1371 (Box 32, Folder 1348)
  - Sturdy, E.W., 1882; cuid1372 (Box 32, Folder 1349)
  - Sturgis, Russell (1836-1909), 1874; cuid1373 (Box 32, Folder 1350)
  - Styles, Fanny, undated; cuid1374 (Box 32, Folder 1351)
  - Suess, Edward (1831-1914), 1896-1899; cuid1375 (Box 32, Folder 1352)
  - Sutter, John Augustus (1826-1897), 1873-1874; cuid1376 (Box 32, Folder 1353)
  - Swallow, Georse Clinton (1817-1900), 1868; cuid1377 (Box 32, Folder 1354)
  - Taintor, Charles Micaiell (1817-?), 1870-1875; cuid1378 (Box 32, Folder 1355)
  - Tarr, H.G.H., 1876; cuid1379 (Box 32, Folder 1356)
  - Tarrant, J.F., 1870-1871; cuid1380 (Box 32, Folder 1357)
  - Taylor, Cadet, 1882; cuid1381 (Box 32, Folder 1358)
  - Taylor, Charles W., 1887; cuid1382 (Box 32, Folder 1359)
  - Taylor, G.L., 1884; cuid1383 (Box 32, Folder 1360)
  - Taylor, G.W., 1868; cuid1384 (Box 32, Folder 1361)
  - Taylor, James H., 1869; cuid1385 (Box 32, Folder 1362)
  - Taylor, William, 1887; cuid1386 (Box 32, Folder 1363)
  - Taylor, William Alex (1837-1912), 1875; cuid1387 (Box 32, Folder 1364)
  - Teller, Henry Moore (1830-1914), 1883; cuid1388 (Box 32, Folder 1365)
  - Tenney, Sanborn (1827-1877), 1869-1872; cuid1389 (Box 32, Folder 1366)
  - Terrell, Jay, 1874; cuid1390 (Box 32, Folder 1367)
  - Terry, Henry T., 1875; cuid1391 (Box 32, Folder 1368)
  - Terry, James, 1877-1882; cuid1392 (Box 32, Folder 1369)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony (1815-1886), 1882; cuid1393 (Box 32, Folder 1370)
  - Thomas, N.G, 1889; cuid1394 (Box 32, Folder 1371)
  - Thomas, T.H., 1888; cuid1395 (Box 32, Folder 1372)
  - Thomas, W.H.B., 1869; cuid1396 (Box 32, Folder 1373)
  - Thompson, [Charles], 1874; cuid1397 (Box 32, Folder 1374)
  - Thompson, Mary D., 1893; cuid1398 (Box 32, Folder 1375)
  - Thompson, W., 1885; cuid1399 (Box 32, Folder 1376)
  - Thornson, James (1815-1892), 1876; cuid1400 (Box 32, Folder 1377)
  - Thurston, Robert Henry (1834-1903), 1884; cuid1401 (Box 32, Folder 1378)
  - Tice and Lynch, 1898; cuid1402 (Box 32, Folder 1379)
  - Tiffany, A.S., 1879-1891; cuid1403 (Box 32, Folder 1380)
  - Tiffany and Company, 1899; cuid1404 (Box 32, Folder 1381)
  - Tindell, Charles W., 1901; cuid1405 (Box 32, Folder 1382)
  - Topinard, Paul (1830-1911), 1888; cuid1406 (Box 32, Folder 1383)
  - Torrer, Alphonse, 1872-1873; cuid1407 (Box 32, Folder 1384)
  - Torrey, David (1818-1894), 1869; cuid1408 (Box 32, Folder 1385)
  - Towner, H.C., 1877-1878; cuid1409 (Box 32, Folder 1386)
  - Townsend, George Henry (?-1869), cuid1410 (Box 32, Folder 1387)
  - Tracey, John G., 1875; cuid1411 (Box 32, Folder 1388)
  - Travers, Henry H., 1872; cuid1412 (Box 32, Folder 1389)
  - Trouessart, E.L., 1879-1896; cuid1413 (Box 32, Folder 1390)
  - Trowbridge, John (1843-1923), 1894-1895; cuid1414 (Box 32, Folder 1391)
  - Trowbridge, William Petit (1828-1892), 1884-1890; cuid1415 (Box 32, Folder 1392)
  - Trubner and Company, 1881-1888; cuid1416 (Box 32, Folder 1393)
  - True, Frederick William (1858-1914), 1885-1897; cuid1417 (Box 32, Folder 1394)
  - Trumbull, James Hamond (1821-1897), 1886; cuid1418 (Box 32, Folder 1395)
  - Tucker, G.H., 1855; cuid1419 (Box 33, Folder 1396)
  - Turner, Thomas J., 1879; cuid1420 (Box 33, Folder 1396A)
  - Turner, William (1832-1916), 1885-1897; cuid1421 (Box 33, Folder 1397)
  - Tuttle, Morehouse, and Taylor, 1875-1885; cuid1422 (Box 33, Folder 1398)
  - Twichell, Joseph Hopkins (1838-1918), 1869-1897; cuid1423 (Box 33, Folder 1399)
  - Tyndall, John (1820-1893), 1879-1881; cuid1424 (Box 33, Folder 1400)
  - Tyson, Philip Thomas (1799-1877), 1867; cuid1425 (Box 33, Folder 1401)
  - Uhler, Philip Reese (1835-1913), 1866-1888; cuid1426 (Box 33, Folder 1402)
  - Ulrich, Edward Oscar (1857-1944), 1894; cuid1427 (Box 33, Folder 1403A)
  - U.S. Geological Survey, 1892-1894; cuid1428 (Box 33, Folder 1403B)
  - Utterback, W.H., 1890-1891; cuid1429 (Box 33, Folder 1404)
  - Van Beneden, F.T., 1881; cuid1430 (Box 33, Folder 1405)
  - Van der Brook, Ernest, 1899; cuid1431 (Box 33, Folder 1406)
  - Van Name, Addison (1835-1922), 1874; cuid1432 (Box 33, Folder 1407)
  - Van Tyne, N.C., 1887; cuid1433 (Box 33, Folder 1408)
  - Vandegrift, F.B. and Company, 1898; cuid1434 (Box 33, Folder 1409)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius (1843-1899), 1895-1896; cuid1435 (Box 33, Folder 1409A)
  - Varney, A.L., 1872; cuid1436 (Box 33, Folder 1410)
  - Vaux, Calvert (1824-1895), 1866; cuid1437 (Box 33, Folder 1411)
  - Veltman, R., 1871-1876; cuid1438 (Box 33, Folder 1412)
  - Verill, Addison Emery (1839-1926), 1871-1892; cuid1439 (Box 33, Folder 1413)
  - Vibert, Charles W., 1891; cuid1440 (Box 33, Folder 1414)
  - Viener, Carl, 1892; cuid1441 (Box 33, Folder 1415)
  - Vining, Edward Payson (1847-1920), 1883; cuid1442 (Box 33, Folder 1416)
  - Virchow, Hans (1852-?), 1893; cuid1443 (Box 33, Folder 1417)
  - Vogdes, Anthony Wayne (1843-?), 1873-1874; cuid1444 (Box 33, Folder 1418)
  - Volkhausen, A, 1886; cuid1445 (Box 33, Folder 1419)
  - Vaorhies, I.C., 1869-1874; cuid1446 (Box 33, Folder 1420)
  - Voy, C.D., 1872; cuid1447 (Box 33, Folder 1421)
  - Wachsmuth, Charles, 1886; cuid1448 (Box 33, Folder 1422)
  - Wadsworth, James Wolcott (1846-1926), 1871; cuid1449 (Box 33, Folder 1423)
  - Wakefield, George W., 1887-1899; cuid1450 (Box 33, Folder 1424)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1868-1886; cuid1451 (Box 33, Folder 1425)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1891; cuid1452 (Box 33, Folder 1426)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1892; cuid1453 (Box 33, Folder 1427)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1893; cuid1454 (Box 33, Folder 1428)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1894; cuid1455 (Box 33, Folder 1429)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1895; cuid1456 (Box 33, Folder 1430)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1896; cuid1457 (Box 33, Folder 1431)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1897; cuid1458 (Box 33, Folder 1432)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1898 January - April; cuid1459 (Box 33, Folder 1433)
  - Walcott, Charles Doolittle (1850-1927), 1898 May - 1899; cuid1460 (Box 33, Folder 1434)
  - Walker, Edward C., 1868-1892; cuid1461 (Box 33, Folder 1435)
  - Walker, Francis Amassa (1840-1897), 1873-1896; cuid1462 (Box 33, Folder 1436)
  - Walker, Thomas Alfred (1862-1935), 1876; cuid1463 (Box 33, Folder 1437)
  - Wallace, Alfred Russell (1823-1913), 1878-1887; cuid1464 (Box 33, Folder 1438)
  - Wallace, G., 1872; cuid1465 (Box 33, Folder 1439)
  - Wallace, John, 1872-1875; cuid1466 (Box 33, Folder 1440)
  - Walsingham, Thomas de Grey (1843-1919), 1881-1897; cuid1467 (Box 33, Folder 1441)
  - Walton, Walter, 1879; cuid1468 (Box 33, Folder 1442)
  - Ward, Frank A., 1889-1898; cuid1469 (Box 34, Folder 1443)
  - Ward, George A., 1895-1898; cuid1470 (Box 34, Folder 1444)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1868-1870; cuid1471 (Box 34, Folder 1445)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1871-1872; cuid1472 (Box 34, Folder 1446)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1873-1874; cuid1473 (Box 34, Folder 1447)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1875-1876; cuid1474 (Box 34, Folder 1448)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1877-1879; cuid1475 (Box 34, Folder 1449)
  - Ward, Henry Augustus (1834-1906), 1880-1898; cuid1476 (Box 34, Folder 1450)
  - Ward, Henry L., 1897-1899; cuid1477 (Box 34, Folder 1451)
  - Ward, Lester Frank (1841-1913), 1894-1898; cuid1478 (Box 34, Folder 1452)
  - Ward, Lester Frank (1841-1913), 1898-1899; cuid1479 (Box 34, Folder 1453)
  - Ward, Walter G., 1888; cuid1480 (Box 34, Folder 1454)
  - Ware, R.M., 1870-1871; cuid1481 (Box 34, Folder 1455)
  - Waring, Arthur B., 1874; cuid1482 (Box 34, Folder 1456)
  - Waring, George Edwin (1833-1898), 1878; cuid1483 (Box 34, Folder 1457)
  - Warman, Philip Creveling (1859-1908), 1890-1896; cuid1484 (Box 34, Folder 1458)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley (1829-1900), 1883; cuid1485 (Box 34, Folder 1459)
  - Warren, Gouverneur Kemble (1830-1882), 1877; cuid1486 (Box 34, Folder 1460)
  - Waterbury, W.S., 1896-1897; cuid1487 (Box 34, Folder 1461)
  - Waterous, Thomas C., 1896; cuid1488 (Box 34, Folder 1462)
  - Watson, Edward, 1887; cuid1489 (Box 34, Folder 1463)
  - Watson, L, 1873-1874; cuid1490 (Box 34, Folder 1464)
  - Webster, Arthur Gordon (1863-1923), 1886; cuid1491 (Box 34, Folder 1465)
  - Webster, R.J., 1870; cuid1492 (Box 34, Folder 1466)
  - Welch, Theodore F., 1869; cuid1493 (Box 34, Folder 1467)
  - Weld, Mason Cogswell (1829-1887), 1877; cuid1494 (Box 34, Folder 1468)
  - Welling, C.L.D., 1893; cuid1495 (Box 34, Folder 1469)
  - Wells, H.F., 1893-1894 April; cuid1496 (Box 34, Folder 1470)
  - Wells, H.F., 1894 May - December; cuid1497 (Box 34, Folder 1471)
  - Wells, H.F., 1895; cuid1498 (Box 34, Folder 1472)
  - Wells, H.F., 1896-1897 July; cuid1499 (Box 34, Folder 1473)
  - Wells, H.F., 1897 August - December; cuid1500 (Box 34, Folder 1474)
  - Wells, H.F., 1898 February - May; cuid1501 (Box 34, Folder 1475)
  - Wells, H.F., 1898 June - November; cuid1502 (Box 34, Folder 1476)
  - Wells, H.F., 1898 December; cuid1503 (Box 34, Folder 1477)
  - Wells, H.F., 1899 January - October; cuid1504 (Box 34, Folder 1478)
  - Wells, Mrs. H.F., 1899; cuid1505 (Box 34, Folder 1478A)
  - Wells, J.M., 1876; cuid1506 (Box 35, Folder 1479)
  - Wells, W.S., 1877; cuid1507 (Box 35, Folder 1480)
  - Welsh, William, 1875-1877; cuid1508 (Box 35, Folder 1481)
  - Wertheimber, L., 1897-1898; cuid1509 (Box 35, Folder 1482)
  - Westbrook, Richard Ward (1864-1932), 1880-1887; cuid1510 (Box 35, Folder 1483)
  - Wetherby, A.G., 1877; cuid1511 (Box 35, Folder 1484)
  - Wetmore, George Peabody (1863-1940), 1869-1898; cuid1512 (Box 35, Folder 1485)
  - Whaler, Thomas, 1873; cuid1513 (Box 35, Folder 1486)
  - Wheatley, Charles M., 1868; cuid1514 (Box 35, Folder 1487)
  - Wheeler, Charles Gilbert (1836-1912), 1876-1879; cuid1515 (Box 35, Folder 1488)
  - Wheeler, C.L., 1876; cuid1516 (Box 35, Folder 1489)
  - Wheeler, George Montague (1842-1905), 1871-1876; cuid1517 (Box 35, Folder 1490)
  - Wheeler, John Davenport, 1884; cuid1518 (Box 35, Folder 1491)
  - White, Andrew Dickson (1832-1918), 1893; cuid1519 (Box 35, Folder 1492)
  - White, Charles Ablather (1826-1910), 1869-1894; cuid1520 (Box 35, Folder 1493)
  - White, E.W., undated; cuid1521 (Box 35, Folder 1494)
  - White, J., 1877; cuid1522 (Box 35, Folder 1495)
  - White, Thomas R. Jr., 1890; cuid1523 (Box 35, Folder 1496)
  - Whitefield, Robert Parr (1828-1910), 1868-1887; cuid1524 (Box 35, Folder 1497)
  - Whitney, Eli (1847-1924), 1877; cuid1525 (Box 35, Folder 1498)
  - Whitney, Henry Mitchell (1843-1911), 1873; cuid1526 (Box 35, Folder 1499)
  - Whitney, Josiah Dwight (1819-1896), 1872; cuid1527 (Box 35, Folder 1500)
  - Whitney, William Collins (1841-1904), 1885; cuid1528 (Box 35, Folder 1501)
  - Whittaker, John, 1871; cuid1529 (Box 35, Folder 1502)
  - Whitten, J.H., 1871; cuid1530 (Box 35, Folder 1503)
  - Whittier, John G., 1856; cuid1531 (Box 35, Folder 1503A)
  - Whittridge, Worthington (1820-1910), 1880-1887; cuid1532 (Box 35, Folder 1504)
  - Wieland, George Reber (1865-1953), 1896-1898; cuid1533 (Box 35, Folder 1505)
  - Wieland, George R., 1898 August - September; cuid1534 (Box 35, Folder 1506)
  - Wieland, George R., 1898 October - 1899 January; cuid1535 (Box 35, Folder 1507)
  - Wilder, Burt Green (1841-1925), 1875-1887; cuid1536 (Box 35, Folder 1508)
  - Wilder, Thomas B., 1889; cuid1537 (Box 35, Folder 1509)
  - Wiley, S.L., 1892; cuid1538 (Box 35, Folder 1510)
  - Willcox, Joseph, 1890; cuid1539 (Box 35, Folder 1511)
  - Willcox, N. A., 1899; cuid1540 (Box 35, Folder 1512)
  - Willcox, Samuel A, 1882; cuid1541 (Box 35, Folder 1513)
  - Willcox, Washington F., 1892; cuid1542 (Box 35, Folder 1514)
  - Willey, George P., 1874; cuid1543 (Box 35, Folder 1515)
  - Williams, A.R., 1869; cuid1544 (Box 35, Folder 1516)
  - Williams, Albert (1852-1914), 1882; cuid1545 (Box 35, Folder 1517)
  - Williams, Henry Shaler 0847-1918), 1877-1893; cuid1546 (Box 35, Folder 1518)
  - Willis, E., 1870; cuid1547 (Box 35, Folder 1519)
  - Williston, Frank H., 1878-1880 May; cuid1548 (Box 35, Folder 1520)
  - Williston, Frank H., 1880 June - November; cuid1549 (Box 35, Folder 1521)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1876; cuid1550 (Box 35, Folder 1522)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1877 March - June; cuid1551 (Box 35, Folder 1523)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1877 July - October; cuid1552 (Box 35, Folder 1524)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1877 November - December; cuid1553 (Box 35, Folder 1525)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1878; cuid1554 (Box 35, Folder 1526)
  - Williston, Samuel Wendell (1852-1918), 1879-1885; cuid1555 (Box 35, Folder 1527)
  - Williston, Thomas, 1872; cuid1556 (Box 35, Folder 1528)
  - Willson, Edmund B., 1889-1890; cuid1557 (Box 36, Folder 1529)
  - Wilson, Edward, 1889-1890; cuid1558 (Box 36, Folder 1530)
  - Wilson, George C., undated; cuid1559 (Box 36, Folder 1531)
  - Wilson, J.N., 1866-1869; cuid1560 (Box 36, Folder 1532)
  - Wilson, Thomas (1832-1902), 1896; cuid1561 (Box 36, Folder 1533)
  - Winchell, Alexander (1824-1891), 1866-1874; cuid1562 (Box 36, Folder 1534)
  - Winkler, Tiberius Cornelius (1822-1898), 1881-1896; cuid1563 (Box 36, Folder 1535)
  - Winnett, F.B., 1882; cuid1564 (Box 36, Folder 1536)
  - Winslow, J.C., 1876-1879; cuid1565 (Box 36, Folder 1537)
  - Winthrop, Robert Charles (1809-1894), 1866-1887; cuid1566 (Box 36, Folder 1538)
  - Wise and Ripley, 1877; cuid1567 (Box 36, Folder 1539)
  - Wolcott, C., 1892-1895; cuid1568 (Box 36, Folder 1540)
  - Wolcott, Mabel E., 1892-1896; cuid1569 (Box 36, Folder 1541)
  - Flood, M.W., 1876; cuid1570 (Box 36, Folder 1542)
  - Woodbury, William H., 1875; cuid1571 (Box 36, Folder 1543)
  - Woodman, H.T., 1869; cuid1572 (Box 36, Folder 1544)
  - Woodward, Arthur Smith (1864-?), 1892-1897; cuid1573 (Box 36, Folder 1545)
  - Woodward, Ellen S., 1899; cuid1574 (Box 36, Folder 1546)
  - Woodward, Henry (1832-1921), 1875-1893; cuid1575 (Box 36, Folder 1547)
  - Woodward, Henry (1832-1921), 1894-1899; cuid1576 (Box 36, Folder 1548)
  - Woodward, R.B., 1871; cuid1577 (Box 36, Folder 1549)
  - Wooley, J.B., 1899; cuid1578 (Box 36, Folder 1550)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight (1801-1889), 1868; cuid1579 (Box 36, Folder 1551)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Salisbury (1852-1929), 1876; cuid1580 (Box 36, Folder 1552)
  - Worhen, Amos Henry (1813-1888), 1871-1877; cuid1581 (Box 36, Folder 1553)
  - Wortman, Jacob L., 1879-1881; cuid1582 (Box 36, Folder 1554)
  - Wright, Arthur Williams (1836-1915), 1871; cuid1583 (Box 36, Folder 1555)
  - Wright, Bryce M., 1871-1873; cuid1584 (Box 36, Folder 1556)
  - Wright, Bryce M., 1874-1877; cuid1585 (Box 36, Folder 1557)
  - Wright, Edward Perceval (1834-1910), 1887; cuid1586 (Box 36, Folder 1558)
  - Wright, W.G., 1883; cuid1587 (Box 36, Folder 1559)
  - Wurts, Charles Pemberton (1859-?), 1903; cuid1588 (Box 36, Folder 1560)
  - Wyckoff, William, 1874; cuid1589 (Box 36, Folder 1561)
  - Wyman, Jeffries (1814-1874), 1862-1872; cuid1590 (Box 36, Folder 1562)
  - Yarrow, Henry Crecy (1840-1929), 1874-1875; cuid1591 (Box 36, Folder 1563)
  - Yates, Lorenzo Gordin (1837-1909), 1872-1889; cuid1592 (Box 36, Folder 1564)
  - Youmans, William Jay (1838-1901), 1876; cuid1593 (Box 36, Folder 1565)
  - Youmans, Edward Livingston (1821-1887), 1882; cuid1594 (Box 36, Folder 1566)
  - Young, Charles Augustus (1834-1908), 1882-1894; cuid1595 (Box 36, Folder 1567)
  - Zeltner, A. de, 1872; cuid1596 (Box 36, Folder 1568)
  - Ziegler, Harry D., 1872; cuid1597 (Box 36, Folder 1569)
  - Zittel, Karl Alfred, ritter von (1839-1904), 1880-1896; cuid1598 (Box 36, Folder 1570)
- Marsh family, 1817-1900; Series II
  The family materials are divided into "Family correspondence" and "Special files." The former is arranged alphabetically by the last name of the writer and family correspondents include Marsh, his grandfather, father, mother, stepmother, aunts, uncles, and sisters. The "Special files" contain family material other than correspondence--including memorabilia, legal papers, property inventories, receipts, photographs, copybooks, and newsclippings--and are arranged by specific family member.The earliest family letter is dated fourteen years before Othniel's birth, and his mother's special file Also included in the family correspondence are letters from Marsh to his uncle, George Peabody, and others, referencing the projected Peabody Museum at Yale, and memorabilia of Marsh's German sojourn. From the date of his appointment to the chair of paleontology at Yale in 1865 until his death, Marsh received no salary, presumably because it was expected that he would be one of George Peabody's heirs.
  - Family Correspondence
    - Caleb Marsh
      - Brown, Anson, 1827 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Brown, Daniel B., 1827 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Cass, Lewis, 1831 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Chadwick, George, 1824 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Chapel, Daniel, 1834 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Chapel, Maria, 1826 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Choate, Rufus, 1841 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Daniels, Judith D.P.R., 1825-1861 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - DeLong, Francis, 1856 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Dixon, Eliza
        See: Marsh, E.D
      - Foster, Asron, 1824 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Greenleaf, Benjamin, 1824 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Helmick, George, 1838 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Johnston, John F., 1821 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Lattin, Mary
        See: Marsh, Mary L.
      - Lattin, Wright, 1835-1837 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Little, Elbridge, 1834 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Little, George P., 1863 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Little, Sophronia Peabody, 1829-1846 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Lockport Journal, 1828 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Marsh, Eliza Dixon, 1844-1858 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Marsh, Ezekiel, 1824-1831 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Marsh, Ezekiel, 1832-1842 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Marsh, George E., 1856 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Marsh, James, Sr., 1856-1857 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Marsh, James, Jr., 1856 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Marsh, John, Sr., 1834-1844 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Marsh, John, Jr., 1817-1824 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Marsh, John, Jr., 1827-1856 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Marsh, Martha Lattin
        See: Martha L. M. Walker
      - Marsh, Mary, 1839-1859 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Marsh, Mary G. Peabody, 1825-1834 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Marsh, Mary Lattin, 1836 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Marsh, Mary Peabody
        See: Waters, Mary P. Marsh
      - Marsh, O.C., 1847-1865 (Box 38, Folder 31 - 34)
      - Metcalf, Rev. W., 1844 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Parker, Benjamin, Jr., 1827 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Peabody Riggs Co., 1833-1836 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Peabody, David, 1831-1840 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Peabody, George, 1821-1856 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Peabodv, Jeremiah D., 1820-1833 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Peabody, Judith Dodge
        See: Daniels, Judith D.P. Russell
      - Peabody, Mary Gaines
        See: Marsh, Mary G.P.
      - Peabody, Thomas, 1832 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Reen, John R., 1828-1829 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Reynolds, James R., 1856-1857 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Rohinson, Christopher, 1838 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - Russell, Jeremiah, 1833-1850 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - Russell, Judith Dodge Peabody
      - Silliman, Rev. W., 1848 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - Taggatt, William, undated (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - Tuck, Samuel, 1856 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - Walker, Martha L. Marsh, 1858 (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - Waterbury, William E., 1835 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - Waters, Mary Peabody Marsh, 1839-1849 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - Waters, Mary Peabody Marsh, 1850-1852 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Waters, Robert H., 1851-1858 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - Wilcox, Benjamin, 1848-1853 (Box 38, Folder 54)
      - Williams, M., 1817 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Caleb Robert Marsh